http://www.reverse.org/admin/privacy-policy/

Online Privacy Policy
This web site is operated by Liberty Reverse Mortgage (“Liberty”). We are committed to respecting your privacy and value your trust. This privacy notice tells you what information we collect, how we use it and how we protect it.
Online Information Collection
You can visit us on the World Wide Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself, including your e-mail address. In this case, our web servers collect the name of the domain you used to access the Internet, such as “aol.com” or “yahoo.com,” as well as the web site you came from and the web site you visit next.
We may select outside companies who provide services on our behalf and use this information in the course of delivering advertisements to you and to measure the number of visits, average time spent, page views, and other statistics about visitors to our web site, in general. We may also use this data to monitor site performance and to make the site easier and more convenient to use.
We may aggregate statistics that we gather about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and services, and provide these statistics to third parties. However, when we provide these statistics to third parties, they will not include any personal information that identifies you, unless you have agreed to receive personally-tailored information.
When you fill out a form on our web site, such as the Calculator or the Contact Us form, we collect information to help us answer your inquiry. This may include but is not limited to, information such as: property value, mortgage value, age of youngest borrower, first name, last name, phone number, street address, zip code and email address.
Online Information Disclosure
There are instances in which your personal information is shared with third parties and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share the information you have provided to us through this web site.
We may disclose personal information we collect on this web site to others that provide services to you. Disclosure of personal information to these service providers is done to better serve you.
We may disclose identifying information collected on this web site, such as name, address, and phone number, within the Liberty family of companies to fulfill your requests, or offer other products and services we think may be of interest to you.
We may make additional disclosures of information as permitted or required by law. For example, we may disclose information to law enforcement agencies or state insurance authorities.
If you choose to complete an online form, such as the Calculator, Contact Us, or other Information Request, one of our Reverse Mortgage Advisors may contact you, or we may share your information with a third party Reverse Mortgage originator whom we believe can provide you with the information you have requested regarding your Reverse Mortgage needs. Once your information has been shared, their privacy policies will govern how they use and disclose your information. If you do not want your information to be shared, please do not complete an online form on this web site.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of data stored by your internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. We, along with thousands of other web sites, use cookies to enhance your web viewing experience and to measure your web site usage. With the help of cookies, we may present you with customized offerings or content that may be of interest to you. We may also use cookies to recognize you on subsequent visits or to remember your user name so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being sent. Please note by not accepting cookies, you may limit the functionality we can provide to you when you visit our site.
Links to Other Web Sites
We are not responsible for the information collection practices of other web sites when you link to them from our web site. We cannot guarantee how those parties use cookies or whether they place on your computer cookies that may identify you personally. You should carefully review the privacy policies of each web site you visit to understand how they collect, use, and disclose information.
Information from Children
We do not knowingly solicit information from children and we do not intentionally market our products or services to children.
E-mail Communications
Occasionally, we may send you e-mail communications with information that may be useful to you, including information about our products and services or about offerings from other affiliated companies or third parties. You will be given the option of not receiving any such e-mail messages, if you choose.
Encryption
We use encryption and authentication tools to protect information we gather on our web site. E-mail communications outside of our web site, however, may not be protected. If you are sending us an e-mail communication that includes highly confidential information, such as a credit card number, you may want to call us or send it by regular mail.
Access
In some cases, you may be able to update certain information that you provided to us. This may require you to use a unique user name and password (or “PIN”). Also, where the capability exists, you may request that we modify or delete information we have gathered during your visit to our web site.
Visitors/Registered Users
As a visitor to our web site, you may have access to certain features without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. We will not gather any information about you when you are using these features. We may require you to become a registered member in order to gain access to and use other features. Once you become a registered member, we may collect personal information when you use our web site.
The practices and policies contained in this Privacy Policy replace all previous notices or statements with respect to the same subject.
This Privacy Policy will not apply to your relationships with companies that are not affiliated with Liberty Reverse Mortgage, such as banks and independent insurance agents. Their privacy policies will govern how they collect, use and disclose personal information that you allow them to access.
This Privacy Policy applies only to the information collection practices of this web site.
Our Privacy Policies — Our Commitment to Customers
Consumers purchasing (or applying for) a product or service from Liberty Reverse Mortgage are subject to the privacy policy of the company. If multiple products or services are purchased or applied for, the privacy policy of the company collecting the data applies. Customers who purchase our products and services will be provided with the privacy policy for each company to which they provide personal information.
Our Security Procedures
We maintain procedures and technology designed to prevent unauthorized access to personal information. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural protections in accordance with applicable standards to protect personal information. We restrict access to personal information to employees and service providers for legitimate business purposes to assist in providing products or services to you. Employees who violate our Privacy Policy are subject to disciplinary action.
Opting Out
You may opt-out of information sharing by choosing not to complete any of the online forms on this web site. Please note that by completing those forms you are consenting to receive contact from a reverse mortgage originator who will provide you with the information you have requested. If you do not wish to receive contact, or have your information shared with one of our partners, please do not complete any of the forms on this web site.
Change In Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to modify or supplement our Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes, we will post our current Privacy Policy on our web site.
California Consumer Privacy Act
Liberty Reverse Mortgage WEBSITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE
Legal Notices
Please Read These Terms Carefully Before Using This Site
Liberty Reverse Mortgage (“Liberty”) provides this website (the “Site”), subject to the following Terms and Conditions of Use, which may be updated by us from time to time without notice. This Site provides you with certain services, including but not limited to, access to information about the products and services offered by Liberty and may provide you with information regarding other financial and consumer services and products offered by Liberty, its affiliates (“Affiliates”), and other third party providers (“Providers”). Use of this Site and the services are subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use and all applicable laws. Certain areas within this Site may be subject to additional or different terms and conditions of use, which are posted in those areas. Not all of the services and materials described on this Site are available for use in all geographic areas of the United States where Liberty conducts business. By using the Site, you agree to abide by all of the terms and conditions set forth in this notice. Unless stated otherwise, any new services and materials added to this Site also will be covered by these Terms and Conditions of Use.
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OR CONDITIONS, DO NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THIS WEBSITE OR ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THIS WEBSITE. YOUR ACCESS AND USE OF THIS WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO ABIDE BY EACH OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH BELOW.
Limited License
Subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement, Liberty grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited right to access, use and display this Site and the materials thereon. You agree not to interrupt or attempt to interrupt the operation of the Site in any way. Liberty authorizes you to view and download the information (“Materials”) at this Site only for your individual use. This authorization is not a transfer of title in the Materials and copies of the Materials and is subject to the following restrictions: 1) you must retain, on all copies of the Materials downloaded, all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the Materials; 2) you may not modify the Materials in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose (other than for your own benefit); and 3) you must not transfer the Materials to any other person. You agree to abide by all additional restrictions displayed on the Site as it may be updated from time to time.
No Offer
THE INFORMATION ON THIS SITE IS NOT AN OFFER BY OR ON BEHALF OF LIBERTY OR ITS AFFILIATES TO SELL OR SOLICIT AN OFFER TO BUY ANY SECURITY, ANNUITY OR INSURANCE PRODUCT.
No Professional Advice
The information available on the Site is intended to be a general information resource regarding the matters covered, but is not offered as legal, accounting, tax or other financial advice, and is not tailored to a customer’s specific circumstances. ALL INFORMATION, OPINIONS AND ADVICE AVAILABLE ON THIS SITE SHOULD BE EVALUATED IN CONSULTATION WITH A LEGAL, ACCOUNTING, TAX, INVESTMENT OR OTHER FINANCIAL SPECIALIST.
Copyrights/Trademarks
This Site, including all Materials, is copyrighted and protected by worldwide copyright, trademark and intellectual property laws and treaty provisions. You agree to comply with all such laws worldwide in your use of this Site and to prevent any unauthorized copying of the Materials. Except as expressly provided herein, Liberty does not grant any express or implied right to you under any patents, trademarks, copyrights or trade secret information. Liberty, Liberty Reverse Mortgage and the Liberty logo are service marks/trademarks of Liberty Reverse Mortgage.
DISCLAIMER
YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT: (1) YOUR USE OF THIS SITE AND THE SERVICES AND MATERIALS PROVIDED AT THE SITE ARE AT YOUR SOLE RISK, AND (2) THE MATERIALS MAY CONTAIN INACCURACIES AND TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. LIBERTY, ITS AFFILIATES AND THE PROVIDERS DO NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THE MATERIALS OR THE RELIABILITY OF ANY ADVICE, OPINION, STATEMENT OR OTHER INFORMATION DISPLAYED OR DISTRIBUTED THROUGH THE SITE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ANY RELIANCE ON THE MATERIAL OR ANY OPINION, ADVICE, STATEMENT, MEMORANDUM, OR INFORMATION SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK.
LIBERTY, ITS AFFILIATES AND THE PROVIDERS (AS TO THEIR MATERIALS ONLY) RESERVE THE RIGHT, IN THEIR SOLE DISCRETION, TO CORRECT ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY PORTION OF THE SITE. WE USE REASONABLE EFFORTS TO PROVIDE YOU WITH ACCURATE INFORMATION. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT, HOWEVER, TO MAKE CORRECTIONS AND/OR CHANGES SHOULD THIS INFORMATION PROVE TO BE INACCURATE. LIBERTY, ITS AFFILIATES AND THE PROVIDERS (AS TO THEIR MATERIALS ONLY) MAY MAKE ANY OTHER CHANGES TO THE SITE, THE MATERIALS AND THE PRODUCTS, PROGRAMS, SERVICES OR PRICES (IF ANY) DESCRIBED IN THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
THIS SITE, THE SERVICES, INFORMATION AND MATERIALS ON THE SITE AS WELL AS ANY SOFTWARE MADE AVAILABLE ON THE SITE, ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT PERMIT THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES. THEREFORE SOME OF THE EXCLUSIONS ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Limitation of Liability
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT LIBERTY, ITS AFFILIATES AND THE PROVIDERS WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES, COSTS OR LOSS OF PRODUCTS, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITIES OF THOSE DAMAGES, RESULTING FROM: (i) YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, THE SERVICES, OR MATERIALS, OR (ii) OBTAINING SUBSTITUTE PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES, OR (iii) THE USE OF ANY DATA, INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OBTAINED FROM TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH THE WEBSITE, OR (iv) ANY STATEMENT OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY, OR (v) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATED TO THE SITE, THE SERVICES OR MATERIALS. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT PERMIT THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. THEREFORE, SOME OF THE LIMITATIONS ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Third Party Sites
As a convenience to you, Liberty and its Affiliates may provide, on this site, links to websites operated by other entities. If you use these sites, you will leave this site. If you decide to visit any linked site, you do so at your own risk, subject to that site’s terms and conditions of use and privacy policy that may be different from those of this Site. It is your responsibility to take all protective measures to guard against viruses or other destructive elements you may encounter on these sites. Liberty and its Affiliates make no warranty or representation regarding, and do not endorse, any linked websites or the information appearing thereon or any of the products or services described thereon. Links do not imply that Liberty, its Affiliates or this Site sponsors, endorses, is affiliated or associated with, or accessible through the links, or that any linked site is authorized to use any trademark, trade name, logo or copyright symbol of Liberty or any of its affiliates or subsidiaries.
External Links to the Site
All links to the Site must be approved in writing by Liberty, except that Liberty consents to links in which: (i) the link is a text-only link containing only the name “Liberty Reverse Mortgage”, (ii) the link “points” only to www.libertyreverse.com and not to deeper pages: (iii) the link, when activated by a user, displays that page full-screen in a fully operable and navigable browser window and not within a “frame” on the linked website; and (iv) the appearance, position, and other aspects of the link may neither create the false appearance that an entity or its activities or products are associated with or sponsored by Liberty nor be such as to damage or dilute the goodwill associated with the name and service marks/trademarks of Liberty or its Affiliates. Liberty reserves the right to revoke this consent to link at any time in its sole discretion.
Viruses
There is always the possibility of unknowingly acquiring computer viruses on the Internet and thus we want to warn you about infections or viral contamination on your system. It is your responsibility to scan any and all downloaded materials received from the Internet. Liberty and its Affiliates are not responsible or liable for any damage caused by viruses or related hazards, whether or not that virus or hazard resulted from a visit to this Site. You, and not Liberty or its Affiliates, assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair, or correction related to computer viruses.
Information Provided By You
In order to use certain Services on this Site, you may have to register. You agree to provide true, accurate and current information about yourself as prompted by the registration and application forms on this Site. If any information you provide is untrue, inaccurate, incomplete or not current, or if Liberty or any Affiliate has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, incomplete or not current, Liberty, in its sole discretion, has the right to suspend or terminate your access to the Site. Further, you agree that Liberty will not be liable to you or any third party if Liberty terminates your access to the Site, and the Services or Materials thereon, for any reason.
Except for the information you submit during the registration process or during the use of any other service offered through this Site (the “Permitted Information”), Liberty and its Affiliates do not want you to, and you should not, send any confidential or proprietary information to Liberty or its Affiliates via the Site. You agree that any information or materials that you or individuals acting on your behalf provide to Liberty or its Affiliates other than the Permitted Information will not be considered confidential or proprietary. By providing any such information or materials to Liberty or its Affiliates, you grant to Liberty and its Affiliates an unrestricted, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, display, publicly perform, transmit, distribute and sub-license to others such information and materials, and you further agree that Liberty and its Affiliates are free to use, and allow others to use, any ideas, concepts or know-how that you or individuals acting on your behalf provide to Liberty or its Affiliates. You further recognize that Liberty and its Affiliates do not want you to, and you warrant that you shall not, provide any information or materials to Liberty or its Affiliates that is defamatory, threatening, obscene, harassing, or otherwise unlawful, or that incorporates the proprietary material of another.
Liberty and its Affiliates will use the Permitted Information in accordance with the privacy policy posted on this Site.
Notices
Notices from Liberty and its Affiliates to you regarding your use of the Site, the Services and Materials will be made by e-mail or regular mail, in the sole discretion of Liberty or the applicable Affiliate, unless otherwise required by law or contract.
General Terms
Liberty reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove any portion of these Terms and Conditions of Use in whole or in part, at any time without notice; you should periodically revisit this Site to review the current terms and conditions by which you are bound. Changes in these Terms and Conditions of Use will be effective when posted. Your continued use of the Site, the Services and Materials after any changes to these Terms and Conditions of Use are posted will be considered acceptance of the changes.
Liberty and its Affiliates may terminate, change, suspend or discontinue any aspect of the Site, including the availability of any features of the Site, at any time without notice. Liberty and its Affiliates may also impose limits on certain features and services or restrict your access to all or parts of the Site without notice or liability. Liberty and its Affiliates may terminate the authorization, rights and license given above.
The Terms and Conditions of Use constitute the entire agreement between Liberty, its Affiliates and you in connection with your use of this Site, the Services and the Materials. Any cause of action you may have with respect to your use of this Site, the Services or the Materials must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. If for any reason an arbitrator or a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of these Terms and Conditions of Use or portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to effect the intent of these Terms and Conditions of Use, and the remainder of the Terms and Conditions of Use shall continue in full force and effect. In the event of termination, the disclaimers and limitations of liabilities set forth in the Terms and Conditions of Use will survive.
The Terms and Conditions of Use will be deemed to include all other notices, policies, disclaimers and other terms contained in this Site and in other contracts that you may have executed with Liberty and its Affiliates.
International Users and Choice of Law
This Site is controlled, operated and administered by Liberty from its offices within the United States of America. Liberty and its Affiliates make no representation that materials at this Site are appropriate or available for use at other locations outside the United States and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use the Site or export the Materials in violation of U.S. export laws and regulations. If you access this Site from a location outside the United States, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws.
Governing Law
These Terms and Conditions of Use shall be governed by the laws of the State of California, United States of America, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions.
Requirement of Written Agreement
The purchase or sale of mortgage loan products, insurance and/or securities between Liberty, its Affiliates and their customers are governed by written policies or contracts. The terms of these policies or contracts are binding on the parties. No other representation, whether made in person, online, electronically (including, but not limited to, representations on this Site), in writing, or by graphic or verbal communication may alter the terms of those policies or contracts.
Legal Notice
The material on this website is for informational purposes only and it covers a variety of topics on residential home mortgages, insurance and other financial products and services. Although some of the information involves tax, legal, accounting or similar issues, neither Liberty Reverse Mortgage or its affiliated companies offering the products or services nor their agents or affiliates are in the business of offering such advice. In addition, advice on such matters must fit your particular circumstances. Consequently, we strongly encourage you to consult with your own professional advisors to examine the legal, tax, accounting or investment aspects of any information presented on this website and how they may affect your particular situation.
THIS SITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR DISTRIBUTION TO, OR USE BY, ANY PERSON OR ENTITY IN ANY COUNTRY OR JURISDICTION WHERE SUCH DISTRIBUTION OR USE WOULD BE CONTRARY TO LOCAL LAW OR REGULATION. BY OFFERING THIS SITE AND INFORMATION, OR ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES VIA THIS SITE, NO DISTRIBUTION OR SOLICITATION IS MADE BY LIBERTY REVERSE MORTGAGE OR ITS AFFILIATES TO ANY PERSON TO USE THIS SITE, OR SUCH INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES IN JURISDICTIONS WHERE THE PROVISION OF THIS SITE AND SUCH INFORMATION, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IS PROHIBITED BY LAW.
The products and services described on this website:
are available only to consumers in the United States of America unless otherwise specifically noted;
may not be available in all states of the USA; and
are subject to all applicable laws and regulations.
THE FINANCIAL OBLIGATIONS OF INDIVIDUAL MORTGAGE INSURANCE OR TITLE INSURANCE PRODUCTS OR POLICIES ARE THE SOLE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE UNDERWRITING COMPANY. NEITHER LIBERTY REVERSE MORTGAGE NOR ANY OTHER AFFILIATES OF THE UNDERWRITING COMPANY ARE LEGALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR PRODUCT/POLICY OBLIGATIONS.
The information contained on this website is inherently limited in scope and may change without notice. The information also does not contain all of the applicable terms, conditions, limitations or exclusions of the products or services described.
Copyright Notice.
Except as otherwise noted on this website, the contents of this website are copyrighted ©2020 by Liberty Reverse Mortgage. All rights are reserved. No part of the materials on this website, including website text, graphics and html code, may be reproduced or transmitted in any form by any means without the express written consent of Liberty Reverse Mortgage.
Reverse Mortgage Information
Reverse Mortgage Calculator
What is a Reverse Mortgage?
Pros and Cons
How Does a Reverse Work
